Finding Aid for the Edwin Hamlett Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous Publications:
  - Rat, Oct. 1968 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Rat, Jan. 12-Jan. 29 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Reader’s Digest, Sept. 1962 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Real Paper, Aug. 30, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Religion and Race (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Red Papers (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Red Worker, Oct. 1971 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - REI Catalogue, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Report on Youth Employment, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Rolling Stone, Mar. 25 1976 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Root and Branch, Jun. 1970 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Root and Branch: nos. 2, 3 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Rough Times, Mar./Apr./May/Dec. 1974 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Sanity, Feb. 1966 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Dec. 1973-Apr. 1974 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Aug. 1974-May 1978 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Mar. 1975-Jul./Aug 1975 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Sept. 1975-Mar. 1976 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Apr. 1976-Nov. 1976 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Dec. 1976-Mar. 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Apr. 1977-Sept. 1977 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Oct. 1977-Jan 1978 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - SAM (Southern Appalachian Ministry in Higher Education), Feb. 1978-Apr. 1980 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Scientific Investor (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Screw: no. 55 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - SESAC Music: Autumn, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Skandaloni: Fall, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Slam: vol. 2 no. 3 and vol. 3 no. 2 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Smear (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Social Justice (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Forum: Spring, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Socialist Forum: Fall, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Sour Grapes (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - South Today, Nov. 1969- Mar. 1970 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - South Today, Mar. 1971- Apr. 1972 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Southern Changes, Aug./Sept. 1982 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Southern Exposure: Spring, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Southern Exposure: Summer/Fall, 1973 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Southern Exposure: Winter, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Southern Exposure: Spring/Summer, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Southern Exposure: Winter, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Southern Exposure: Spring, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Southern Exposure: Winter, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Southern Exposure: Winter, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Southern Regional Council Report, Feb. 1968 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Southern Regional Council Report, Mar. 1968 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Southern Regional Council Report, Mar. 22, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Southern Regional Council Report, Apr. 4, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Southern Regional Council Report, Oct. 1969 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Southern Schools: Misc. Pubs/Reports (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Southern Schools: Misc. Pubs/Reports (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Southern Schools: Misc. Pubs/Reports (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Southern Schools: Misc. Pubs/Reports (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Southern Schools: Misc. Pubs/Reports (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Southerners and Schools Report (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Space City News, Nov. 1969 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Spur Newsletter, Jul. 22, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Stag Line: by Lorimer (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - State and Mind: Winter, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Submarine Church Press: Summer, 1972 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Summary of I-440 Community Workshops, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - SUPA, Dec. 1965 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Sylvia Porter’s Personal Finance, Jul./Aug. 1988 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Taipan: Spring, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Time: Jan 5, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee Driver’s Manual (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee Earth Advocate, Jun., Sept., Oct. 1976 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Tennessee Global Security (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Vanderbilt Photography Review (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Vanderbilt Photography Review (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Views Care Courier Vol. X No. 8 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Voice, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Voice for Jobs and Justice (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Wageless Slave and the Proletariat (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Washington Monthly, Nov. 1972 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Weavings: III, 7 Jan. 1988 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - When Southerners Unite to save their Region by Clark Woodroe (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Why Black History?: The Rightness of Whiteness (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Why did RCP USA Split? (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Will to Survive by Anthony Dunbar (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Win with Love Jun. 1971 no. 5 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Women’s Free Express, Jun- Sept. 1964 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Women’s Liberation Issue 22 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Worker, Feb./Mar. 1978, Jul. 1965 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Workers Viewpoint, Sept. 1974 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Workers Viewpoint, May ‘75 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Workers Viewpoint: 2:1 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Workers Viewpoint: 2:2 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Worker’s World, Mar. 1978 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Working for a Living: 1 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Working for a Living: 2 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Working for a Living: 2 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Working for a Living: 3 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Working for a Living: 4 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Working Papers for a New Society Fall, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Working Parents, Aug./Sept. 1984 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - World Situation: by Paul Tillich (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Young Socialist, Jul./Aug. 1965 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Your Best Protection: The Union Contract (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Your Business Success Through Accounting (Box 88, Folder 14)